[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "And you said that you heard the tape several times, is that mainly listening to it on TV?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "How significant is this late breaking decision to allow Trayvon Martin's toxicology report including his cannabis use to be made available to the court?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "'MARA: Well, good evening, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "We don't know, for example, whether he had taken cannabis, do we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "No, we don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Did you ever instruct your attorney, Ben Crump -- you didn't have Ben Crump when you listened to tape on the 27th or the 28th, did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Crump", "Ben Crump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "He was not your attorney at that point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "No, he wasn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Did you instruct your lawyer to say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "I never instructed anyone to say anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "You never instructed Ben Crump to say the police had lied about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I never instructed anyone to say anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Crump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Did you instruct your lawyer Ben Crump to say that the audio has since been cleared up and now you can hear it better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Crump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Is it really effective for you and the defense to go after a man in that position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I think you have to be very careful and very sensitive to the loss that a grieving family is going through.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Which way is he running?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Down toward the other entrance to the neighborhood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Which entrance is that that he's heading towards?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "The back entrance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Are you following him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "In his head, he is looking at Trayvon Martin and thinking bad things about him, isn't he, indisputably?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "A couple of things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Where do you see the last few days of this case going now, Mark, and in particular, the big question, I guess, will you put George Zimmerman on the stand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Well, I've been asked that a lot, and I -- I have to wait until I convinced myself that the state has proven their case beyond a reasonable doubt before we would consider ever putting George Zimmerman on the stand.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last few days"], "PERSON": ["Mark", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "How concerned are you about that and about the safety of your client should he be declared an innocent man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Well, first of all, my client will never be safe because there are a percentage of the population who are angry, they're upset and they may well take it out on him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon"]}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Mr. Martin, even at this time, is it hard for you to believe that your son is not longer living?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RBR", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "It's very difficult to believe that Trayvon's not living.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "What is your response to that decision?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Well, number one, I think the law had to be followed and the judge had to allow it in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Is it likely that your partner Ben Crump will give evidence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, you know, yesterday I took Ben's deposition.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Crump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Why should we -- well, is it, though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Because if it was definitive proof that it was one or the other, that is the case right there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "But do you agree with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "And what did he progress to as a boxer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "TO", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, he never got off of learning how to punch so not very far.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Yes or no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "No, they -- they created a terrible problem for themselves by overcharging second-degree murder.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oliver Wendell Holmes"]}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "What will the repercussions be of this, whatever happens with the verdict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, Oliver Wendell Holmes once said that hard cases make bad law.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Why didn't he just announce who he was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "He should have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Alan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Not guilty of second-degree murder.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Judge Alex?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "I think not guilty of second-degree murder, and I think that if they reject self-defense, he gets a manslaughter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Jayne?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Not guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Obviously, although race, everyone's trying to exclude it from this case, it's been hanging there as an overbearing presence, hasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "It has been hanging there and it's been there since the beginning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "NNS", "VBN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "What is your view of how they should react if that eventuality happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Well, certainly I think you're correct that many in the black community as well as throughout the country are very upset by what has trans transpired, particularly because this is a murder case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "And he's profiling, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Well, I think it's clearly profiling, the question is, what was the basis for the profile.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$64,000"]}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "$", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Why was this plane traveling so, as it turned out, fatally slowly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Now, that's the $64,000 question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "And if they did, could it be malfunction by the plane?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Well, that's still possible and sometimes these investigations take some strange turns as they go down the line but right now clearly all the focus is on the performance of the crew and investigators can't say pilot error.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "And does the public have a right to know before they board a plane exactly who will be at the wheel and how much experience they've had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "AGER: Well, I suppose you could say that, that the public has a right to know it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130708pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Is there anything other than the fact that it was a tragic accident that couldn't have been avoided?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "That would be a horrible tragedy and the coroner said he isn't going to release the full autopsy reports for a couple of weeks anyway.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]